Hi, my name is Yingxi,
I studied in Beijing University of Technology as an undergraduatestudent in computer science.
During the time in Beijing, I got consecutive Learning MeritScholarships.
And be selected as an exchange student to study in ECE Paris.
During the time inParis, I did a lot of projects working with data,
For example our startup project in school.
The goal of this project is to allow clients shopping in market without needing the help ofassistant.
What he needs is just a smartphone application in order to scan product and payonline.
As for me I did the ruby on rails server for data management storage and exchange,
I found that working with data is very interesting and I would like to continue working on it.
What’s more, I also did two internships in France, one in UNESCO and the other in  PSA,
From these 2 internships, I got deeper understanding of how tocooperate with team members in the same project,
and I learnt many innovative ideas.
Finally, I got my master degree in this engineer school and acquired many practical skills.
I have been in New York in 2013 to visit my host family after finished my summer study in UCI.
I found that there are plenty of opportunities in New York since its location priorities.
My host sister live in Brooklyn, we first met each other in Beijing during high school timesince she came to study Chinese.
Nearly 10 years passed, she came to China to teach as avolunteer and I went to US to study,
If I could be selected to study in NYU then it’s really agood chance to visit them again and to better maintain this friendship.
After attained a master Degree, I would like to work in an international IT company,
which can provides me opportunity to use both my networking knowledge,
and communication skills.
I see myself developed my management skills during the training program offered byuniversity.
So after working for few years, accumulate experience,
my goal is to develop myself in leadership area,
which can help me better understand the architecture ofenterprise and the management principles.
Laying the foundation for my future career.
Finally, I would like to start my own business.
Since I have multiple international backgrounds,
I will make full use of the knowledge I learnt in different countries,
get ready to grow in frustration and learn from mistakes.
Developing myself, get myself stronger day by day,
and do my best to make my company as a fortune 500 in the last.
Thank you for watching, I do hope that I could be selected to NYU
Merci beaucoup(Thank you so much), Au-revoir(Bye) :)